We have touch down.
Donor is on site.
I repeat. Donor is on site.
The donor signed the releases, cleared?
We are cleared
Atention. Donor in route to main lab.
All tech personnel please report
to the operating theatre
I repeat. All tech personnel please
report to the operating theatre
Ready
Time since cardiac death?
7 hours 15 minutes
Proceed
Neural tissue intact.
Protoplasmic integrity looks good.
We have a viable cortex.
Do you concur?
I concur
Ball's in your court, William
This man is dead
Yet his neurological
data is still accessible
We are going to take his biological brain
imprint it into that synthetic brain
replicate the human mind
Ed, boot the mapping sequence
Optical positioning optimal
- Target acquired
- Lacrimal targetting complete
- Standby to engage neural probe
- Standby for neural probe
Standby
Initiating transfer
Main drive is online
- Ok mapping confirmed
- Remove the donor
Standby to initiate the neural imprint
Initiate
Scott, try protocol Alpha-9, please.
Parietal.
Thank you
Temporal and axon online. Good.
Frontal bone online looking good
Okay
Connect protocol 345
801 two-phase application
P1. Site parameters - AP insula.
Primary action.
Stasis modality. Exception.
And translate.
Finalised. Confirmed.
All states, go.
All functions. Go.
Imprint complete
Margaret, energise the body.
Sergeant Kelly
Do you hear me?
Sergeant
Who am I
Sergeant, you've transitioned
to a synthetic body
Try to relax. You're coming online.
It will take some time
- Who am I?
- Sergeant, try to relax.
Who am I?
Sergeant
Sergeant! Sergeant Kelly!
- Who am I?!
- Sergeant Kelly!
Turn it off, the imprint failed.
Severed the override
Who am I?
RTX. Proceed to 07.
- It spoke.
- They've done that before.
No they vocalised before. Make noise.
- This one spoke.
- And I can't tell you
how amazing that would
have been 8 months ago.
Today it just annoys the shit out of me
- It's progress. Undeniable progress.
- In my world progress is measured in results.
Which we don't have
The truth is I'm not sure how much longer
I can keep the lights on
Turns out colossal and repeated failure
Tends to spook shareholders. Who knew?
This is my life's work
I've moved my family here. Made sacrifices.
I promise you, I am this close.
Well. That just isn't
close enough is it, Bill
But don't let it ruin
your weekend or anything
Oh shit
- I'm sorry I'm late
- It's okay
- How is it going, honey?
- The kids haven't even packed
Daddy!
Zoe!
- How is it going? How's your day?
- Matt!
Not in the house, I know
Told him not stop spying me with that thing
- It is called a spy-drone
- Okay
So go pack now. Don't jump on the furniture
- Hola, Foster family!
- Ed!
- Hey, nugget
- Hey, can you feed him once a day
but don't overfeed him
I'll show you the food, come on
Okay
- Hey, you talked to Jones?
- Something like that
Okay, what did he say? Did you get fired?
- What's "fired"?
- I didn't get fired
- Who got fired? -Daddy
- What?
Nobody got fired
- I thought you were a gonna, man
- Wait, what's going on?
Our test subject ripped itself apart
earlier today It was pretty brutal
What's "brutal"?
It spoke, Mona. 345 the test subject
- It actually spoke
- It spoke?
If it could speak then it could feel
We shut it down as soon as possible
You can just keep bringing
people back from the dead
until you have this stuff worked out
How many times have you had a
patient flatlined in the ER
and you brought them back?
My patients don't rip themselves apart
She's got a point there, William
I should probably food
find Sophie for the fish
William, honey, I believe in you
But I don't like where this is headed
People could suffer
The first heart transplant
patient survived 18 days
- He suffered. Was that wrong?
- No
I'm on the verge of a breakthrough, Mona
Soldiers, accident victims, alzheimers
Lives won't have to be cut short
But something's preventing the synthetic
from achieving consciousness
Maybe there's more that makes it human
Like a soul
We're the some told of
what is happened to us
and how we processed it
that's what it make us such
- It's all neurochemistry.
- Do you really believe that?
That's all I am? Your children?
Just pathways, electrical
signals and chemistry?
You have kids that love you
and a wife that adores you
And we have a scientist
Do you think I should quit?
Hi -Hi -Hi
I'm just worried you're losing sight
of what's right and wrong
I won't. Trust me
Okay have fun
I'm gonna get you back
- What's the boat called again?
- It's called the Cheatin' Hussy
- Daddy!
- Keys are in the bait box
- We don't do that
- Daddy!
Thanks. See you on Sunday night
Everybody in?
Seat belts
The Foster family ferry to
funtown is ready to sail
Yay!
Really, dad
Hoist the mainsail, Cap.
I spied with my little
eyes something that is
Bored. There is possibly adopted.
That would be me
Hey dad, when we get there
can we go fishing on a boat?
Absolutely
Are we almost there?
We could wait for the boat to float by
You know what they say
If you don't like the
weather just wait 5 minutes
I can't see anything
Can you see anything?
I feel that we should pull over
- Okay? Everybody okay?
- Holy shit!
That was close
What?
- Mum! -Mona!
- Mummy!
Daddy!
Mona?
Kids?
Oh god
Sophie? Matt? Zoe?
Zoe. God help my baby girl
Mona?
No
William? What's up? What's going on?
I told you no questions
- Where is it?
- It's all in the back
Oh shit
William, what the hell happened man?
I need you to do
something for me, Ed
Oh no. No way I can't
They are not gone. Not yet
William, we need to call the police
or something man, I mean
- William, what the hell?
- Boot the mapping sequence
We cannot do this man
Boot the mapping sequence, Ed
Edward Whittle access granted
Okay just because I think I can do it
doesn't necessarily mean I can, okay
There is a reason human cloning is banned
And just because it's hard to do,
- It's only half the issue here
- Just let me know what we need
Look William, I know you've
been through hell but
you need to understand something here
The first few animals I
cloned came out blind
Their skulls were deformed
Their internal organs they
weren't internal anymore, man
That's what a mistake here means
And if we've made a mistake I need to know
if you're prepared to terminate
Just won't make a mistake
Okay
Those are pods
Can I clone a human being, technically,
yeah, it's possible
But look, William, if this works
their brains are gonna
come out like infants
Okay. A total blank slate
and not to put salt in a wound
but you've exactly worked out all
the kinks for transferring a mind
Do I need to remember you what's
happened every single time you've try?
We've transferred biological to
biological on cloned animals, Ed
- Rats, monkeys
- Not human beings, man
You've seen it. We can do it
What if something horrible goes wrong?
Something already has
Ed, nobody can know what happened
I need you to get rid of the bodies
- William, I don't know if
- I'm begging you
I can't do it
Okay
I'll meet you at the house
What's in the barrels?
Components. Building blocks
Amino acids, fructose, accelerants
You know just a ton of -
Everything you need to build a you
There are only 3 pods
- I need 4 pods
- Yeah, I know there weren't 4
- I need 4 pods, Ed
- I can maybe get another one
in the next quarter maybe
Do not tell me that there aren't 4
What do you want me to do here?
These pods are $1.7m each
I'm not a freaking genie here okay
I can not just sneeze out another pod
Sorry, William
William?
You're alright?
Pick a name
No no
Not enough pods
- Pick a name
- No way, man
You pick it
- Please, god dammit, please pick a name
- William, no no
- Pick a name!
- No, this one's on you
You wanted this you pick it
You pick the damn name
You gotta watch the levels.
The levels are everything
I seeded the pods with their DNA, but you
gotta keep an eye on them all the time
Never leave them alone
If the chemical balance isn't
maintained the clones will die
and we can't just start over
So you need to watch the levels
Okay and they'll all be done
at the same time, right?
Okay
Shit, this is got a lot more difficult
Tell me you can do that
- Yeah, just got to compensate something
- Ed
Yeah it can be done
Where is your backup generator?
- In case we lose power
- I don't have a generator, Ed
- Okay
- Is there something I should know?
Yeah, the pods can't lose power. Ever.
If there's a 7-second power interruption
that will throw off all the levels
and I just told you how important
those things are, so yeah,
we need a generator
- It's 2am nothing's open
- Shit man, I don't know.
What do you want from me? I
can't think of everything
I am so far in over my head at this point
And so are you man you know that
Is there anything else?
No, I think that's it
That is a lot of batteries
In 17 days they are coming out
You got till then
to figure out how to
give them consciousness
If by some miracle we can pull this off
What about Zoe?
Every memory they had is in here
I'll delete her
I'll delete the memories
You can do that?
Humans lose memories all the time
Beta amyloid proteins.
Neurofibrillary tangles
I'll corrupt the memory
Upload a new neural map
They'll never remember her
We are going straight to hell
- Thank you
- Good luck, man
Search parameters: Zoe
Delete pathways and associations?
Deleted
Mr. Foster, this is the police
Morning, officers
Do you speak Spanish? No, sorry
Well, pardon my English
I am Officer Perez, this is Rodriguez
We're following up on
some recent car robberies
Somebody stolen the batteries
out of every car on the block
How odd
Did they get you too?
No, they didn't
You're the lucky guy
Yeah
Nothing out of the ordinary
If you see anything or anybody suspicious
- let us know
- Will do, officer
Have a good day
Okay. Alright.
That happens
Edward
I feel compelled
to comment on the noticable
lack of Bill around here
Wouldn't happen to know
anything about that, would you?
Just said that he had pneumonia
Walking pneumonia
- Walking?
- With pneumonia, yeah
Would you convey a message for me?
I spoke to the board today
Unless 345 works, we'll gonna shutdown
at the end of the quarter
Shutdown?
Would you like a nice reference letter?
Yeah, I'm sure he'll be in soon
You know, William, he's got
a very strong immune system
Test topics 221. Update
Transfer of consciousness from original
subject to clone. Successful
And consciousness can be transferred
Why not human?
What am I missing?
- William
- Yeah?
Hey, I just talked to Jones,
and he said that if we
don't get 345 working
- He's gonna shut us down
- Oh shit
Yeah and there's $8.7m worth of
Bionyne equipment in your basement
If he shut us down they
gonna come looking for it
And you want to know
scientific term for that?
Royally and utterly boned
- So what are we going to do?
- Okay, get over here
- What? Wait, where? There?
- Yeah, here
- Why?
- I got to go to work, you got to watch the pods
- Okay man, you don't have to yell
- I'm not yell-
Okay, sorry, I was yelling
- Just hurry up and you have pneumonia
- What?
Dr. William Foster access granted
There he is. Hi, Bill
You look like hell
Can I get anything?
Maybe something herbal?
What do you have exactly?
- Pneumonia
- What a chupa
You're here
I need you to review the data links
before I can work on 345 neural junctions
- Yeah look, not now
- Jones's all over us
William, we are waiting for your okay on the
MF interface for the server replacements
- Get in line
- Okay
You're alright?
- I'm fine, why?
- No reason
- Hello?
- I'm sorry about Matt
You don't remember me?
Matt's teacher, Mrs. Barnes
I can explain
Your cousin told me. Sorry
to come by unannounced
but Matt hadn't been to school a few days
and I couldn't get to your
wife on her cellphone
And I know we're not supposed
to have favorites, but
Well I hope that clears everything up
- Happy Holiday
- Happy Holidays
- Is she gone?
- What happened?
She said she had to go to the bathroom She
was banging on the door for like 5 minutes
like a psychopath, I don't know
what was I supposed to do?
What did you say? I said
that Matt had chickenpox
and that he went to stay
with his grandparents
His grandparents are dead, Ed.
How am I going to explain that?
I dont' know, William
Don't drag me into your giant
sucking hole of lies, okay?
You didn't call the
school make something up?
No
What about the clinic that Mona works at?
It's been 5 days
You didn't think that anyone would have
noticed your entire family was missing?
- I have a lot of things on my mind, Ed
- Yeah, sorry
- You gonna have to deal with that
- How are they?
They are a foot taller
Really?
I don't think so
You think they really
going to shut us down?
All I know is we need this robot ready
before the next donor arrives
Well, where's William?
No, I don't want to hear anymore excuses
What am I missing?
Jesus, man. You look like
you're up to nefarious shit.
And that's not a good look for someone who's
actually up to nefarious shit by the way.
- I'm not ready
- No, I said 17 days
It's been 17 days. There
is no "I'm not ready" here
Ed
Ed!
- Shit
- Ed
Ed!
Did you see that?
I still don't know why it happened
If I don't know what causes it
how can I be certain it
won't happen to them?
Yeah
You have to thought about it 17 days ago
The accelerants follow the
DNA profile precisely
You keep them in the tanks
they keep aging
Your wife, 2 weeks from
now, cancer, maybe?
Your daughter. Menopause?
Your son. I don't know.
Male pattern baldness and
a droopy old man sack
My point is, in a couple of days
even if you do figure this out
they would have aged years beyond
the age they were when they die
How are you going to explain that?
How are you not freaking
out right now, William?
- I'm trying to think
- Okay, good
Yeah, sure. You think. I'll think too
I'll think about what's it like in jail
Or when Bionyne sues us for $30b
What are you doing?
I'll sedate them. Induce a coma
That will keep their minds in a blank state
Till I figure it out
What if you don't figure it out?
You can't keeping them sedated
for more than 72 hours tops
After that you going to have
to make a very tough decision
Drain the pod
Got her?
Holy shit.
I did it!
We did it.
She's perfect man.
It's better than successful
man this is perfect.
Shit.
Okay.
This should keep their bodies fed for a
while and I'll drop somemore off tomorrow
Thank you
You got it
You got 3 days man
Yeah
I'll see you tomorrow
Hey we made clones today
You can add that to your resume
I thought I can do it
Sorry
- What?
- Bill, have you been avoiding my call?
- Bill?
- What?
Do you realize how much money has
been invested in this project?
People are counting on you.
I'm counting on you - Shit
- And we almost out of time
- Holy shit
What did you say?
Do you hear me?
Bill, are you still there?
We've been looking in the wrong place
You're really close to me, man
It's not the mind, it's not the brain, Ed
- It's the body
- The body?
It's so obvious, so elegant, so simple
Hey man, let's pump the brakes
on the crazy train, alright?
Follow me, Edward
Dead flat. Watch this
Her mind is a blank slate. Comatose.
She's never experienced a
moment of consciousness
Yet, she's breathing. Her heart's pumping
But that is not a sign of consciousness.
Those are involuntary functions.
All controlled in the brain
Her brain knows that it has a body
This specific body.
That's what I was missing
That's why 345 doesn't work
It has electrodes and wirings
connected to steel and titanium
We're imprinting a biological
brain into a synthetic mind
But it is doesn't know that
It's looking for its body,
its heart, its lungs
but it can't find them
So the lower reptilian brain freaks out
It thinks that it is
dying, reacts accordingly
and never has a chance
to reach consciousness
Oh shit, yeah
It's like transplant rejection
We just have to trick the synthetic mind
believe that it has its biological
actual flesh and blood body
- That's the solution
- That maybe is 345 solution
but what does this has
to do with your family?
- They are not robots
- It has everything to do with my family
I will imprinting her
mind into her own body
- I know it's going to work
- But are you sure?
I mean we'll only going
to get one shot at this
Standby to initiate the neural imprint, Ed
- Ready?
- Is that ever matter?
Initiate the neural imprint
Commence Bio to Bio protocol
Keep an eye on Mona's sensory cortex. Good
Going temporal
Parietal
Limbic
- Vitals?
- Vitals are good
Okay
This stays good. All functions good
Initiating neural imprint
Incredible
Imprint completed
What's going on, man? Nothing's happening
Can you hear me, Mona?
Shit, she's rejecting it. Oh shit, man.
What are we gonna do?
Wait!
William?
Baby
- William, what are you doing?
- Putting her to sleep
I can't have her and the kids wake up
- to the house like this
- Yeah, good thinking
Do you have any idea what we've just did?
I mean this is the single greatest
thing that I have ever done in my life
You. Anyone has ever done. I mean
We can't tell anyone about it, but
Oh god.
I mean
We're talking Nobel Prize, right?
Foster-Whittle. Scratch that. Whittle-Foster.
Don't have to be alphabetical
Well, I hope they going to be okay
- We did it
- Yeah
Alright, I'll see you at work
Mona?
Kids?
- Morning, William
- Morning
- So, how is everybody?
- I'm hungry
- Starve
- I feel great. I'm going for a run
- Outside?
- You looked tired. Did you sleep okay?
Yeah
- Have a good run
- Dad!
- Can I have some pancakes?
- Yes
Yes, you can have some pancakes, Matthew
- Sophie, you want some pancakes too?
- Yeah
Great!
Hey, can I have a French toast?
Oui, French toast for the lady
Coming up
Gross
Mom, this milk gone sour.
Did you go shopping?
- I just bought this the other day
- It's curdled
Sold us expired milk
Yeah
Somebody's going to need a piece
of my mind. I'll take care of it
Work
I gotta..
Okay
- Yeah
- Hey, it's me
We got a donor inbound. 37 minutes
- You got to meet me at the lab asap
- My family just woke up
Congratulations, but it's gonna
be a pretty short reunion
unless we solve 345
If we get shut down we get exposed
- Matt, careful
- Are you listening to me?
William, you hearing me?
- Hello?
- Yeah, okay. I'll be there
Goddammit!
Buddy, you're okay?
Yeah, I'm fine
Are you alright?
You don't seemed like yourself today
- I have to go to the lab
- You take off, baby, we're good
I hate to leave you on a Saturday
We'll still be here when you get back
Okay
Neural tissue intact. Protoplasmic
integrity approximately 60%
I make it 55%
Still, cortex is viable. Do you concur?
William?
Negative
It's too corrupt
What's going on, man? Donor was good
I couldn't do it
I couldn't put another person through that
Well, you've picked hell of
a time to grow a conscience
I hope you're ready to go
to jail with your family
Because that's what going to
happen if we don't get 345 to work
So, you better figure something out. Soon
Are you in there, Bill?
- Yeah, it's me
- Everything okay in there?
- All good
- Damn shame about donor today, huh?
We'll get the next one, Sir
I hope there is next one, Bill
Oh my god, shit
- Mom, have you seen my cell phone?
- No I've been looking for mine too
Well, your whole social
life doesn't depend on it
Mine does - Okay, okay, so
where did you have it last?
I have no idea
- Troll, did you take my cell phone?
- No
Oh my god
Ed!
Jesus, are you crying blood?
William, you didn't-
- I did
- On yourself? Are you out of your mind?
Have you considered the very real the
possibility that you've gone completely
insane? It could kill you
Ed, I had to. Listen
I'm going to upload my neural map into 345
- And it's going to be me in there
- Sure
- That makes me-
- Edward. William. -Hey, Phil
We'll start with a scan of my body
I take that data, create an
algorithm which will bridge
with my neural imprint in 345
Okay, so you write an
algorithm that tricks the
synthetic brain into thinking that
its real actual body is there?
Exactly
And with my mind inside, we'll
be able to verify that the
synthetic brain has reached
consciousness because
I will be able to ask myself
I'm the base line, Ed, I'm the control
It will be me
I'll start writing the algorithm tonight
Okay, so we still going to
tree shopping tomorrow?
- Something's wrong
- What's wrong?
I don't know, William, but
something's not right with me
I don't remember what I
had for dinner last night
I don't remember leaving the
clinic for Christmas break
Didn't we go on a boat trip?
I don't remember going
on a boat trip, William
- Something is not right with me
- Oh baby
- Where are the kids?
- Asleep
Sophie has a fever but she's okay
Maybe you have what Sophie has
Maybe
Why don't you go and lie down?
See how you feel in the morning.
Yeah
I'm exhausted
Support directive 2.5
Cytokine 45 NX 1.7
Suppress directive
Mum! Mum!
- Dad!
- Sophie!
- Mum! Is Mom dead?
- What?
- I saw it, Daddy
- No it's just a bad dream
- Mummy's okay
- I saw her die
No. Everything's going to be alright
- Go back to sleep
- It felt so real
It's just a dream, mummy's okay
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, it's okay
It's just a bad dream
- Okay
- Yeah, mummy's all good
Better now
All better
It will be like it never happened
William, what's going on?
- Mona, can we go upstairs?
- What have you done to Sophie?
- I gave her a little sedative
- You did what?
- She's okay
- What?
- Mona, please, let's talk upstairs
- No, William
Tell me the truth
There was a crash
You and the kids died
I brought you back
You're replicants
Get that thing off her head
I'm dead?
You're alive, you are you
Matt is alive upstairs
Sophie and
And no one has to know
How could you do this?
I watched our children die
I held your lifeless body
in my arms and I thought
I could bring you back
What would you have done?
- How're you doing?
- Very good -What's up?
- Morning
- Hi, Ed. How are you?
- Good, how are you?
Great
- Hey Matty, come stay here with me
- But I like this one
No, I hate those were fake
I think they're nice
Come, let's look over here
So you got them back
Yeah
Okay, let's get your tree
Maybe we should move back home
- What?
- We've just settled here
Are you serious, Dad?
- Matt, you missed your plate
- Idiot
What?
Hey Dad, who is Zoe?
Who?
Someone scribbled Zoe in
my closet with a crayon
- There was a bunk bed in that bedroom
- A bunk bed?
- Are you sure?
- I'm not crazy
- I remember photos in the upstairs hallway
- Honey, that thing that happened
There might be some things
And I remember what you
looked like when you're lying
Merry Christmas, Bill
Is that lamb that I smell?
I'm interrupting dinner, aren't I?
- Mona, you look stunning
- I miss you, Jones
Such a lucky man, Bill
What an unexpected pleasure.
Do you care to join us?
Beautiful and generous
I've heard about women like you. Thanks
But I wouldn't dream of imposing
William, can I have a quick word?
Promise I'll have him back in 5 minutes
We're not done
- What brings you by?
- Let me ask you something
Didn't you ever think this
is all a little too easy?
I don't know what you're talking about
Let me help
Subject 346, 347, 348
Bionyne property, Bill
Desperation has driven many great men
to accomplish the impossible
Fate caused that car crash
I just let things play out
Colour me impressed but
now I have a problem
3, actually
Do you know what would happen
if word of this ever got out?
Nobody has to know
- Nobody will ever know
- Mona knows
How long until Sophie and
Matt start asking questions?
Maybe their friends will
Lies are messy
I'm not in a business of messy it's risky
Simple is safe
Those 3 subjects in the wild
is something I cannot tolerate
I know how to make 345 work
That's worth something
Bionyne will be the most successful
biomedical company in the world
William, ask yourself a question
Who would spend this much money saving
mortally wounded soldiers?
Man, come on
That's not how you win wars
- We're not a biomedical company?
- My name isn't even Jones
Now you figure out how to transfer
human consciousness into a machine
Imagine that the best pilot put
into a thousand individual drones
The mind of a hacker loaded into the virus
Do you have any idea how much that's worth?
Bill, isn't that exciting?
What about my family?
Your family died in a car accident, Bill
The algorithm. Get me the algorithm
And then finish dinner.
Kiss the kids good night
Hell. Make love to your wife. Have
what you didn't have the first time
A chance to say goodbye
That is my gift to you
I'll get the algorithm
You see, knew you were smart
enough to do the right thing
This is going to piss me off, isn't it?
William, you are scaring the kids
- Where's Mr. Jones?
- Mum. Dad.
- Are you guys getting a divorce?
- Maybe -No
Can you go to your rooms, please?
- Where's the tin foil?
- On top of the dishwasher
William, I need to know what's going on
And who is Zoe?
Zoe is our daughter
I couldn't bring you all back
I couldn't save you all
There weren't enough pods
I deleted her from your memories
You took the memory of my child from me?
I'm sorry
And I don't blame me if you want to hate me
for the rest of my life,
but now we have to go
Bionyne isn't a medical company
I don't even know what they are
But they going to kill you and the kids
unless we go right now
And I didn't defy every
natural law there is
just to lose you again
We have to go
Kids, we're leaving!
Come on!
What is going on?
Matt, Sophie, there are bad
people trying to hurt us
Just hold on and everything will be alright
We go to Ed's boat and get out of here
I'm disappointed, Bill. Very disappointed
Sir, they're on the move
Don't shoot them in the head
- It's all your fault
- I didn't do anything
How did they find us?
Don't you guys watch TV? I bet you
they tracked Sophie's cell phone
No they didn't, shut up
Shit, maybe it's in the
car, maybe it's the GPS
It's not the car, it's not the phones
Bionyne puts the tracking markers
on all of the experimental animals
The trackers are in you
- William!
- Dad!
We're okay, it's alright
- You're okay?
- We're alight
How do we get the trackers out?
They're in the pods and they
attach to the spine in uteral
They're powered by the central
nervous system. They don't come out
What are you guys talking about?
- Drive to the clinic
- That's about the way we came
Drive to the clinic
Okay
- Sophie, I need you to lie down
- What do you mean?
- Dad why?
- It's ok, get on the table
- It's alright
- What?
The tracker's powered by the nervous
system so this will fry them
- Red, white, black
- Trackers? What are you saying?
- It's okay, Sophie, it's okay
- Mum, what's going on I'm serious?
Somebody put something bad in us
and I'm trying to kill it
I know you're afraid but you just going
to have to try and relax and trust me
It's going to be okay
Mona
If I get this wrong it'll stop her heart
What!? Mum!
This should be it. Inside the hospital
Clear!
Shit, let's go
It's okay, Matty, it's not
as bad as it seems okay
Clear!
- There goes another one
- They gotta be upstairs
Hey! Hey!
What are you doing here?
Dad, hurry up
Baby, try to calm down
Straight ahead on the left
Here
Dad, someone's coming
Damn it
Now
They were right here
Targets are off the axis
they fried their tracers
We lost them
It's Jones, I have a question for you
You and the kids stay in the car
I want to make sure it's safe
I'll see if I can get the boat
Bait box
- When is Dad coming back?
- Honey, stay quiet
The keys are in the bait box
You said the keys are in the bait box
- Mom!
- Let go of me! Mom!
Matt! Mom!
Let go of my kids!
Dad, look out!
Dad!
- William!
- Dad!
We have the wife and kids.
What about Foster?
He will come to us
Good call, Eddy, here're your boat keys
- You bastard
- Mona, look
Everything's going to be fine
if William just cooperates
Fine?
- You idiot. They gonna kill us, Ed
- Mom? What are you talking about?
You know what, I've some snacks
in my office. Take the kids there
Mom! Come with us
Foster's here.
Yes, sir
Look Mona, we stole millions of dollars
worth of Bionyne equipment to make you
- Make me?
- Yes, make you
To bring you back. You died, remember?
I was supposed to get rid of the bodies.
Your bodies
I couldn't do it and then Jones found out
Look, if we just play ball,
we can make it out of this
Get your hands off my wife!
- Where're the kids?
- They're okay, they're over there
William, I'm sorry. This
wasn't supposed to happen
- this got way out of hand
- It's alright
It's going to be okay
- I destroyed the algorithm
- I noticed that
The only place that algorithm
exists is in my head
You want it, we walk out of here
You will never see us again
Me and my family disappear
Bill, are you negotiating?
You need me
Maybe
But I don't need her
Jones, wait!
Or him
Wait, no! I'll do it! I'll do it!
I'll give you the algorithm
I know
If you trust him, he'll kill us
I love you
- The algorithm
- It's all there?
It's all there
Now let my family go
Why are you stuck on that?
This thing
It's a copy
I mean, you really don't get it?
The experiment's over, Bill
No, it isn't
Jones
I'm here for my family
The kids! Let's get the kids
Go
Mom what is he doing? Where is he going?
He's going to get something, Honey
He's going to get something
William!
That's enough
What's it feel like?
This is going to sound strange
But it feels
like me
Bill
I'll die they'll send
somebody else after I'm gone
Sooner or later they'll find you
Not if we work together
Bill, are you negotiating?
What if I told you there
is another way, Jones?
Give us what we want
and you can live again
as a very rich man
What do you say?
Do we have a deal?
See you soon, Bill
I'll handle it from here, William
Are you sure?
You'll have to stay behind
There is no other way
You take care of the family
We'll be fine
Ed
Mummy!
Zoe
Mr. Kisam, I am so glad you could make it
Trust me, you won't regret it
Because I ask you, what price can you
put on a second lifetime?
Please
Well Bill, it's time to go to work
Boot the mapping sequence